<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Part 1: The Beggining of the End on Aetherway</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/</link><description>Recent content in Part 1: The Beggining of the End on Aetherway</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Big Boy</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/big-boy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/big-boy/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;In the local tavern, you could always find Iron. Raised by the elderly on the outskirts of the Hive, he dressed and cut his hair like an old man, with innocent, chubby, rosy cheeks—hence the nickname “Big Boy.” He was as big as a soldier, though he wasn’t assigned as one, and was gentle despite his imposing size. Proud and passionate about his people’s history and culture, he was often seen singing anthems or playing melodies on the war horn he always wore around his neck. His songs would echo through the tavern amid the noise of chatter, laughter, and clinking glasses: “Pon pon pon pon,” he’d cheerfully boom. When asked, he’d share his controversial views, which were regularly challenged. They all knew what he was, and so did he, but he treated everyone with kindness.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Re-Entering the Hive</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/re-entering-the-hive/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/re-entering-the-hive/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;As Fire waited in line to re-enter the Hive, he spotted Boulder among the guards on duty. Assigned by birth as a soldier, Boulder had been raised alongside him, though they’d always had a distant relationship. Fed a different diet than the rest, Boulder was much bigger and tougher-looking. Fire hated his arrogant, overconfident, perpetually-in-challenge-mode face. He would have much rather met someone he didn’t know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Raise your arms!” Boulder said, holding a club in his right hand and avoiding eye contact.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Tattooless Tattooer</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/tattooless-tattooer/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/tattooless-tattooer/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Fire arrived early at the tavern. Besides the owner, the only other person there was Water, the local tattoo enchanter. Sitting with his back to the bar, Water offered Fire some of his Queen’s Reserve honeydew liquor. Fire accepted out of politeness and sat beside him, his stomach churning. Although Water was a familiar figure, they hadn’t spoken before, and Fire struggled to find a topic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You do tattoos for a living, right?”&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Wallet</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/wallet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/wallet/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Fire found a wallet lying on the ground. “Sir, is this yours?” he called out to a scruffy-looking guy who was glancing around nervously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The man looked left and right before responding, “…Yes?” he said hesitantly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fire smirked. “Oh, there’s an ID in here…” He pulled it out, holding it up next to the man’s face for a moment, clearly showing that the two didn’t match at all. “Are you… Blibers Flobers?”&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Wings of Doom</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/wings-of-doom/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/wings-of-doom/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;On a hot summer night, Fire ventured into the heart of the forest, searching for Wind at the place where they had promised to meet after their metamorphosis. Fire had always thought of Wind as a younger brother, and it had been four years since they’d last seen each other. Both had recently gone through their pupal stage, a time of transformation that all Hive People undergo. The air was thick with anticipation; Fire could hear only the gentle rustling of leaves and the sound of his own footsteps through the vegetation. Soon, however, he heard a faint sound—a cry echoing through the trees. Fire called out for Wind several times, but only silence responded.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Fire Explains His Creative Process</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/creative-process/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/creative-process/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meanwhile in His Dimension&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the Queen is mad,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone can feel it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When something goes wrong,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mother must be mad today,”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s what they say.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You know, this vibe everyone in the Hive connects to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of us—well, I know I can—&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;feel what Mother is feeling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But what if I told you there are other vibes you can tune in to?&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Fire Defeats the Broken Thing</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/broken-thing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/broken-thing/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meanwhile in His Dimension&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Fire’s existence, something was always perpetually broken.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No matter how many times he tried to fix it,
it would hold together only for a moment—before breaking again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He examined the broken thing from every angle.
“Why does it keep falling apart?” he wondered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It shouldn’t have been broken, yet it was.
Always in the way, always failing.
“Was that why it was discarded so easily? Like someone else had already given up?”&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Familiarity Fatigue</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/familiarity-fatigue/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/familiarity-fatigue/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Everything he could carry fit into that backpack. Fire leapt into his land sail vehicle, unfurled the sail, and pulled the rope tight against his chest. It was a serene, silent Dawn Day, with a gentle breeze brushing against his face. Before slipping on his goggles, he took one last look at the Hive, its mounds looming quietly in the distance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“As a larva, the Hive felt endless—every crevice a world, every sound a mystery. My first venture into the tunnels was thrilling, full of discovery. But now? It feels small, predictable. Maybe I’ve changed, not the Hive.”&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Spiral</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/the-spiral/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/the-spiral/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;On a Midnight Day, the Captain sat atop the Red Walker’s head, leaning against the beast’s thick fur for support. His usual determined, slightly stern expression remained fixed as he gripped the ropes for steering. In the distance, hundreds of legionaries marched in a synchronized mill formation, their footsteps a faint hum, mingling with the low murmur of voices carried by the wind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Captain removed his hat and placed it over his chest, his voice low with quiet sympathy. “Poor things,” he murmured.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Bargain</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/bargain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/bargain/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The Master of Materialization had been a recurring customer of the Captain’s services for decades, yet their exchanges always carried a peculiar tension. From the top of the Giant Red Walker’s head, under the dim, shifting hues of a Night Day, their conversation took a strange turn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I hear you’re the best Captain alive. Is that true?” the Master asked, his voice smooth, almost mocking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Captain barely glanced at him, his tone dismissive. “That’s just talk.”&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Never Forgotten</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/never-forgotten/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/never-forgotten/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Fire opened the door to the room where all the pieces created by students over the years were kept. His eyes immediately fell on a piece made by a close friend. Scenes of its creation flashed in his mind— all the struggles, but also the moments of mutual support. “What was his name again?” He had left a long time ago, without saying goodbye, without looking back. “I wonder where he is now,” Fire thought. One by one, talented colleagues silently faded away. As he walked through the room, he wondered: how many of them had given up, disappearing into thin air? How many were still around?&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>