<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>Part 1: The Beginning of the End on The Aetherway</title>
    <link>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Part 1: The Beginning of the End on The Aetherway</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 16:46:47 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Big Boy</title>
      <link>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/big-boy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 16:06:26 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/big-boy/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the local tavern, you could always find Iron. Raised by the elderly on the outskirts of the Hive, he dressed and cut his hair like an old man, with innocent, chubby, rosy cheeks—hence the nickname &amp;ldquo;Big Boy.&amp;rdquo; He was as big as a soldier, though he wasn’t assigned as one, and was gentle despite his imposing size. Proud and passionate about his people&amp;rsquo;s history and culture, he was often seen singing anthems or playing melodies on the war horn he always wore around his neck. His songs would echo through the tavern amid the noise of chatter, laughter, and clinking glasses: &amp;ldquo;Pon pon pon pon,&amp;rdquo; he’d cheerfully boom. When asked, he’d share his controversial views, which were regularly challenged. They all knew what he was, and so did he, but he treated everyone with kindness.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One day, using his horn as a drinking vessel, he told Fire how meeting a Flea People music teacher had softened his views: &amp;ldquo;I-I-I’d still r-r-respect him more if he were Hive People, though.&amp;rdquo; Despite their differences, they coexisted peacefully. Big Boy always struggled to find a girlfriend.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Re-Entering the Hive</title>
      <link>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/re-entering-the-hive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 16:33:59 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/re-entering-the-hive/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As Fire waited in line to re-enter the Hive, he spotted Boulder among the guards on duty. Assigned by birth as a soldier, Boulder had been raised alongside him, though they’d always had a distant relationship. Fed a different diet than the rest, Boulder was much bigger and tougher-looking. Fire hated his arrogant, overconfident, perpetually-in-challenge-mode face. He would have much rather met someone he didn’t know.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Raise your arms!&amp;rdquo; Boulder said, holding a club in his right hand and avoiding eye contact.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“C’mon, we’ve known each other since we were larvae,” Fire replied.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“For all I know, you could be a stinky flea person in disguise. Raise your arms!”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Seriously, dude?” Reluctantly, Fire did as ordered. With his left arm, Boulder yanked Fire’s arm up even higher, then hunched down and took a big, deep sniff of Fire’s left armpit. “Turn around,” he said, sniffing Fire’s right armpit next. “Yuck!” he exclaimed with disgust. “Alright, you’re one of us. You may come inside.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Thanks,” Fire said, glaring at him with piercing eyes after the unnecessary, humiliating ordeal. As he passed through, Boulder looked up with a barely contained smirk, his hands placed behind his back, like a soldier at ease.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tattooless Tattooer</title>
      <link>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/tattooless-tattooer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 16:23:22 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/tattooless-tattooer/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Fire arrived early at the tavern. Besides the owner, the only other person there was Water, the local tattoo enchanter. Sitting with his back to the bar, Water offered Fire some of his Queen&amp;rsquo;s Reserve honeydew liquor. Fire accepted out of politeness and sat beside him, his stomach churning. Although Water was a familiar figure, they hadn’t spoken before, and Fire struggled to find a topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“You do tattoos for a living, right?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Yup,” Water said confidently, placing a cigarette in his mouth.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“So how come…”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“You’re wondering why I don’t have any tattoos, aren’t you?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“…Yeah.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“That’s okay; lots of people ask me about it,” he lit his cigarette. “Besides their enchantments, tattoos are typically used as intimidation tactics, right?” He exhaled smoke. “People go for the mean look.” He took a longer drag, his eyes narrowing. “Guess what frightens me the most.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Gee, I don’t kn—”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“A blank canvas,” he cut in, his tone shifting as he fixed a serious, somber stare on Fire.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Wallet</title>
      <link>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/wallet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 17:39:01 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/wallet/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Fire found a wallet lying on the ground. &amp;ldquo;Sir, is this yours?&amp;rdquo; he called out to a scruffy-looking guy who was glancing around nervously.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The man looked left and right before responding, &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;Yes?&amp;rdquo; he said hesitantly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fire smirked. &amp;ldquo;Oh, there’s an ID in here&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; He pulled it out, holding it up next to the man’s face for a moment, clearly showing that the two didn&amp;rsquo;t match at all. &amp;ldquo;Are you&amp;hellip; Blibers Flobers?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The guy fidgeted, avoiding eye contact. &amp;ldquo;Yes, haha, that&amp;rsquo;s me! Good ol&amp;rsquo; Blibers!&amp;rdquo; he replied, his voice a little too high-pitched.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hey, aren&amp;rsquo;t you the one responsible for that big disaster everyone is talking about?&amp;rdquo; Fire probed, raising an eyebrow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The man started sweating. &amp;ldquo;Oohpsi-doopsie, that was me! Don&amp;rsquo;t tell anyone, alright? Now, just give my wallet back, haha!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fire chuckled. &amp;ldquo;Ha, gotcha! I made this name up.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just then, an officer strolled over, hands behind his back. It was Boulder, who was on duty that day. &amp;ldquo;Hey, what&amp;rsquo;s happening here?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Oh, I&amp;rsquo;m glad you&amp;rsquo;re here,&amp;rdquo; Fire replied. &amp;ldquo;We just found this wallet, and we&amp;rsquo;re trying to track down the owner.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Boulder glanced at the ID. &amp;ldquo;Let me see.&amp;rdquo; After a quick inspection, he snorted. &amp;ldquo;What an ugly face. Good luck in your next life.&amp;rdquo; He then pocketed the cash before handing the wallet back to Fire.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Good luck with your quest, sir,&amp;rdquo; the officer said with a dismissive wave as he walked away, still looking up at the sky.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wings of Doom</title>
      <link>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/wings-of-doom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 16:48:01 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/wings-of-doom/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;!--Fix: The way their relationship is stated; The way the date is described. --&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On a hot summer night, Fire ventured into the heart of the forest, searching for Wind at the place where they had promised to meet after their metamorphosis. Fire had always thought of Wind as a younger brother, and it had been four years since they’d last seen each other. Both had recently gone through their pupal stage, a time of transformation that all Hive People undergo. The air was thick with anticipation; Fire could hear only the gentle rustling of leaves and the sound of his own footsteps through the vegetation. Soon, however, he heard a faint sound—a cry echoing through the trees. Fire called out for Wind several times, but only silence responded.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As Fire walked deeper into the woods, shimmering rays of light began to pierce the darkness. He called again, only to hear a desperate voice pleading, “Don’t come! Stay away!” Concerned, Fire replied, “Why? Are you hurt?” Ignoring Wind’s frantic warnings, he pressed on.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In rare cases, some Hive People develop two pairs of beautiful, colorful wings after their second metamorphosis, known as the “Wings of Doom.” Once considered a bad omen, those who possessed these wings were often sacrificed in rituals. Over time, however, the Hive People came to accept this phenomenon, gradually learning to appreciate its mysterious qualities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the edge of a calm river, Fire finally spotted him—hunched over, hands clasped over his head, enormous, radiant wings emerging from his back and reflecting in the water. Dazzled and captivated, Fire called out, “Your wings! They’re incredible! Absolutely breathtaking!”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Don’t look at me!” Wind cried. “They’re disgusting! Hideous! I hate them!” His voice trembled with anguish, punctuated by sobs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Wait, what? Things are different now! You won’t be thrown to the giant beasts!” Fire moved closer, kneeling beside him. “How long have you been hiding them?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Since I went through metamorphosis&amp;hellip; but I guess I always knew&amp;hellip; I always feared them&amp;hellip;” Wind’s voice was filled with despair.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“It’s okay! Everything will be fine,” Fire assured him. “I’m here for you, and I’m sure the others will be, too.” Fire reached out to gently touch Wind’s shoulder, but as he did, he felt a sudden, violent pushback.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“No! You don’t understand! Lady Constant hates them! I’ll pray to Lady Constant until they go away. You have to promise me that you will never tell anyone! No one can know!” Wind’s voice broke with anger and fear, tears streaming down his face.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They never spoke of it again. Fire respected Wind’s wish, but he felt that was the moment their friendship began to unravel. He struggled to understand someone unwilling to embrace their true identity. &lt;em&gt;A goddess who instills such suffering&lt;/em&gt;, he thought, &lt;em&gt;is not a goddess worthy of devotion.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As the years passed, Fire watched Wind—once vibrant and cheerful—slowly consumed by bitterness. Fire found himself wishing Wind would reveal his hidden splendor, but that moment never came.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Looking back, Fire realized that being raised under the strict rules of the Great Order of Order meant that revealing Wind’s wings would risk everything—his social status, his relationships, and the very foundation of his beliefs. It was a testament to Wind’s unwavering faith and commitment to Lady Constant.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps Fire was wrong to assume he knew who Wind truly was. Maybe he had erred in not accepting Wind’s choice. And yet, he couldn’t bring himself to be near the person Wind had become.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire Explains His Creative Process</title>
      <link>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/creative-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 18:20:04 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/creative-process/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meanwhile in His Dimension&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When the Queen is mad,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Everyone can feel it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When something goes wrong,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Mother must be mad today,&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That’s what they say.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You know, this vibe everyone in the Hive connects to.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some of us—well, I know I can—&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;feel what Mother is feeling.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But what if I told you there are other vibes you can tune in to?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire Defeats the Broken Thing</title>
      <link>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/broken-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 16:26:29 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/broken-thing/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meanwhile in His Dimension&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Fire&amp;rsquo;s existence, something was always perpetually broken.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;No matter how many times he tried to fix it,&#xA;it would hold together only for a moment—before breaking again.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;He examined the broken thing from every angle.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Why does it keep falling apart?&amp;rdquo; he wondered.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It shouldn’t have been broken, yet it was.&#xA;Always in the way, always failing.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Was that why it was discarded so easily? Like someone else had already given up?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It felt cursed—&#xA;defiant, mocking, relentless.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;He tried again and again—reinforcing, tightening, rearranging.&#xA;Each time, it seemed to hold for a moment before crumbling again.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Maybe it’s just meant to stay broken,&amp;rdquo; he thought, staring at the scattered pieces.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But something about giving up felt worse.&#xA;Fire’s frustration blazed like a furnace, consuming every ounce of patience he had left with each attempt.&#xA;He even considered total and utter destruction.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Exhausted from the fight, he lay on the ground, defeated.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;I can’t leave it like this,&amp;rdquo; he thought.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;There has to be a way. Starting over would be far too costly.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The solution he avoided lingered in the back of his mind.&#xA;It was risky, and once done, there’d be no undoing it.&#xA;For days, he hesitated, circling the idea like a moth to a flame.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After days of hesitation, Fire finally tried the one thing he had avoided.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;I’ve got nothing else to lose,&amp;rdquo; he said.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And then—what a glorious moment!&#xA;For the first time, he felt like he truly understood the broken thing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It had been held together by hacks and patches,&#xA;but what it truly needed was a permanent solution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The broken thing bore scars of countless repairs,&#xA;but for the first time, it stood firm, resilient in its imperfection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fire sat back, a wave of relief washing over him.&#xA;He felt a quiet sense of accomplishment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Finally,&amp;rdquo; he sighed.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;What else do I need to fix?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Familiarity Fatigue</title>
      <link>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/familiarity-fatigue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 16:04:53 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/familiarity-fatigue/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Everything he could carry fit into that backpack. Fire leapt into his land sail vehicle, unfurled the sail, and pulled the rope tight against his chest. It was a serene, silent Dawn Day, with a gentle breeze brushing against his face. Before slipping on his goggles, he took one last look at the Hive, its mounds looming quietly in the distance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;As a larva, the Hive felt endless—every crevice a world, every sound a mystery. My first venture into the tunnels was thrilling, full of discovery. But now? It feels small, predictable. Maybe I’ve changed, not the Hive.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;He checked his hammer at his belt, then ensured his cloth-wrapped sword—his masterpiece—was secure on the vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The Art of Materialization&amp;hellip; Once thrilling, now fleeting. Creations shrink as fast as they form. I worked through aching hands, fueled by excitement—now the ache lingers, even at rest. Have I lost the magic, or just overlooked the spark?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As the wind carried him from the Hive, he adjusted his goggles and looked back one last time. &amp;ldquo;Did it change, or did I? Maybe with fresh eyes, it would feel vast again. For now, I can only wonder.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiral</title>
      <link>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/the-spiral/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 12:39:18 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/the-spiral/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;!--Note: Fire traveling with the Flea People.--&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On a Midnight Day, the Captain sat atop the Red Walker&amp;rsquo;s head, leaning against the beast&amp;rsquo;s thick fur for support. His usual determined, slightly stern expression remained fixed as he gripped the ropes for steering. In the distance, hundreds of legionaries marched in a synchronized mill formation, their footsteps a faint hum, mingling with the low murmur of voices carried by the wind.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Captain removed his hat and placed it over his chest, his voice low with quiet sympathy. “Poor things,” he murmured.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“What&amp;rsquo;s that? A ritual?” Fire’s voice broke the stillness. He stood behind the Captain, watching the distant figures.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Captain glanced back. “Huh? First time seeing one of these? They don’t teach you about this on your Hive?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Maybe they do. I wasn’t paying attention.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“It’s The Spiral,” the Captain said, turning back to the sight. “They lost the vibe trail to their camp. Now they’re following each other’s vibes.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Legionaries are so dumb. Seems simple to get out,” Fire scoffed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Captain turned sharply, his gaze hard. “That’s not how they perceive it, Fire. You’re not immune to this! Any of us could end up there if we lose our sense of direction. Their reality has warped around them; right now, they’re trapped in cognitive dissonance. At first, they don’t even realize they’re lost. I don’t know how long these ones have been like this, but it can last for weeks—until everyone dies of exhaustion.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A chill ran down Fire’s spine. “So there’s no way out?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“There’s hope, but it’s rare. Very rare.” The Captain’s voice was grim. “And there’s nothing we can do. If you ever see one of these, don’t even think of getting close, or you’ll be drawn into the same vibe! I mean it, Fire—not even a glance.” His tone softened slightly, but his words remained sharp. “And it’s strange you don’t know about this. It’s a key part of the foundation myth of the Hives.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fire frowned, vague memories stirring—a droning Hive teacher reciting the tale like it was some distant legend, far removed from reality. Now, it felt uncomfortably close.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Captain broke the silence, his tone brusque. “Why are you up here, anyway? Don’t you have anything better to do?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bargain</title>
      <link>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/bargain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 12:30:27 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/bargain/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;!--Note: this scene sets up the final conflict at the End of Part 1.--&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Master of Materialization had been a recurring customer of the Captain’s services for decades, yet their exchanges always carried a peculiar tension. From the top of the Giant Red Walker’s head, under the dim, shifting hues of a Night Day, their conversation took a strange turn.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“I hear you’re the best Captain alive. Is that true?” the Master asked, his voice smooth, almost mocking.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Captain barely glanced at him, his tone dismissive. “That’s just talk.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“I hear you can navigate any kind of beast,” the Master continued, undeterred.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Captain crossed his arms, gaze fixed on the horizon. “Red Walkers, Feathered Mountains. Big or small, grounded or flying—it’s all the same in theory. But now, this is my ship.” He patted the Red Walker’s fur with a faint smile. “And I’ll likely be her last Captain. She’s been our home for 1,600 years. I’m not leaving anytime soon.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Master leaned forward, his tone growing sly. “How about… Giant People-Eaters?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Captain’s head snapped toward him, his expression hardening. “Blasphemy! You must be mad! What exactly are you planning?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Master’s lips curled at the edges, his tone still light but carrying an undercurrent of something deeper. “I simply like to know what is possible,” he mused. “And I am a man who finds… possibilities.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Captain exhaled sharply. “You’re playing with fire.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Master’s gaze remained steady, unbothered. “I’ve made a habit of it,” he murmured. “And I always find a way, Captain. Doors open for me, even the locked ones.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the first time, the Captain felt something press against him—not physically, but as if the very space around the Master bent to his presence. The air felt heavier, charged with an unnatural stillness. He ignored it, but the unease lingered, refusing to leave.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Master stepped closer, his shadow stretching unnaturally in the dim light. “You see, Captain, I don’t just open doors. I rewrite the locks.” His grin widened, his confidence unshaken. “I’m a very wealthy and powerful man, Captain. Wouldn’t it be nice if obstacles simply… vanished?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Captain’s lip curled. “You’re sick. I don’t need your money or your tricks,” he spat. He could feel a whisper of doubt coil in his chest, but he crushed it. “I have all I need right here—my home, my crew, my daughter, my family. Everything. A true Captain never leaves his ship.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Master’s smile faltered for a moment, but his unsettling presence only grew stronger. The air around them seemed to ripple, as if reality itself hesitated in his presence. His eyes gleamed with something dark, something the Captain felt but refused to acknowledge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“I always get what I want,” the Master said softly, almost a whisper. “And I always find a way, Captain. Don’t forget who you’re dealing with.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Never Forgotten</title>
      <link>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/never-forgotten/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 16:46:47 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aetherway.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-1/never-forgotten/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Fire opened the door to the room where all the pieces created by students over the years were kept. His eyes immediately fell on a piece made by a close friend. Scenes of its creation flashed in his mind— all the struggles, but also the moments of mutual support. &amp;ldquo;What was his name again?&amp;rdquo; He had left a long time ago, without saying goodbye, without looking back. &amp;ldquo;I wonder where he is now,&amp;rdquo; Fire thought. One by one, talented colleagues silently faded away. As he walked through the room, he wondered: how many of them had given up, disappearing into thin air? How many were still around?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The air felt stagnant, thick with dust and darkened by a heavy, eerie presence. He made a small gesture of respect toward the objects around him, each now resembling a gravestone. &amp;ldquo;It’s a battlefield out there&amp;rdquo;, he thought. &amp;ldquo;But the memories of fallen comrades keep us moving forward.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Standing still, Fire paused, lost in contemplation. “Why am I still here?” he wondered. &amp;ldquo;Talent, skill&amp;hellip; none of it matters. Is believing in yourself even enough?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;He closed his eyes, the silence settling in. &amp;ldquo;Perseverance,&amp;rdquo; he whispered at last. &amp;ldquo;There’s nothing else I could imagine myself doing.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
