<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Part 2: The End of the Beggining on Aetherway</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/</link><description>Recent content in Part 2: The End of the Beggining on Aetherway</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ping Pong Hall</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/ping-pong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/ping-pong/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meanwhile, in Some Dimension…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s a hall of people playing ping pong against mirrors. Unnoticed in the back, a duo plays together.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Owl People</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/owl-people/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/owl-people/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meanwhile, in Some Dimension…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We finally arrived at the museum where the owl people lived. We had all brought gifts for them, as it was typically polite to do so. Overwhelmed by the variety of objects, they rotated their heads completely and, ignoring our presence, kept them fixed toward their backs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The owl people feel comfortable when they are surrounded by things that remind them of their past,” the guide said. “They can only look back because they see no future,” she concluded.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Fall of the Tomato Civilization</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/tomato-civilization/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/tomato-civilization/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meanwhile, in Some Dimension…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I wandered through eerie ruins, I spotted a red figure in the distance. I waved, and they waved back, so I approached. He had a long beard, a staff, and looked like a dried tomato. I asked, “What’s up?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He began a story about how green tomatoes once played there, but a disagreement over whether to say “to-MAY-toh” or “to-MAH-toh” tore the community apart. Friends became enemies, and civil war broke out. “Cherries were the first to go,” he lamented. The real twist? The leaders, who fueled the conflict, were secretly running a ketchup business—and were the same person, disguised with a fake mustache.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Great Vibe Blackout</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/vibe-blackout/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/vibe-blackout/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meanwhile, in Some Dimension…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A mysterious event occurred once, halting interdimensional vibe transmission for hours. Bored, people turned to those nearby for entertainment. Some of the best books were conceived, and even wars were paused. Despite the disruption, it’s fondly remembered by those who experienced it. Once transmissions resumed, life quickly returned to normal.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chest-shaped Heart</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/chest-heart/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/chest-heart/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meanwhile, in Some Dimension…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amid the crowd, a little girl fixated on a heart-shaped object. After hours of holding it, she sat beside me, still staring. I asked, “Is this a chest?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yes, it’s my heart,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s inside?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t know; I don’t have the key.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But there’s no lock—it’s open.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ooooh,” she whispered.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Floating Heart</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/floating-heart/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/floating-heart/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meanwhile, in Some Dimension…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And there it was: the center of the stage, where everyone dreams to be, yet only a few dare to be inevitably consumed by its flames. A girl offered her heart, they took everything else but that.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Labeland</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/labeland/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/labeland/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meanwhile, in Some Dimension…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Navigating through the green hills, I’ve arrived at this place where giant label makers were placed. People would approach them, get a label on themselves, and proceed to the next label maker. The process would repeat endlessly. Some had their bodies completely covered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On top of the hill, a figure without a single label observed the scene with a happy face. I sat by his side and asked, “What’s happening here?”&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Giant Rat</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/giant-rat/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/giant-rat/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meanwhile, in Some Dimension…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the center of the castle, there was a giant, old, and dirty rat, surrounded by treasures of all kinds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It eats cool ideas and poops out old and lame ones. The more it eats, the fatter, lazier, and stinkier it gets.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Why do they keep feeding it?” I asked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It wasn’t always like that. Its poop was once fresh. People got too emotionally attached to it, and now they don’t want to address the stink.”&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Your Reflection Isn't You</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/reflection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/reflection/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meanwhile, in Some Dimension…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was walking through a colonnade, surrounded by what appeared to be shallow waters. In the distance, more colonnades stretched into the horizon, their reflections rippling in the water. Beyond them, the landscape was sparse—perhaps some small trees, but little else. The sunlight was direct and bright, as if it were around noon. Other people walked there too, though whether they were visitors or inhabitants was unclear.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Disposable</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/disposable/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/disposable/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Seating on the floor and resting her head against the bed, Lady Spiral desperately cried, her sobs echoing softly through the room. The Queen appeared in the doorway, her presence filling the space. “Oh honey, don’t cry. Mama is here for you,” she cooed, kneeling beside Spiral. She stroked her hair gently, fingers threading through the strands in a soothing rhythm, but nothing could stem Spiral’s grief. Her sobs continued, unrelenting.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Rooftop</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/rooftop/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/rooftop/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meanwhile, in This Dimension…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Water and Fire lounged on the rooftop after school, sipping drinks from a vending machine, soaking in the Friday vibes as the sun dipped toward the horizon. The world felt alive around them, the warm glow of the setting sun casting long shadows and igniting the sky with hues of orange and purple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fire broke the comfortable silence. “You know, for a moment… after I got hit by that truck, all those dreams I had while I was unconscious felt so real. That world… it felt like the real one. But as I recovered, those memories started to fade, replaced by everything here. I just… I don’t know, I feel like I don’t belong.”&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Lady Thread's Leap</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/threads-leap/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/threads-leap/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meanwhile, in This Dimension…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fire returns to an abandoned theme park, a place once filled with energy and laughter. The layout is unchanged, but the park feels empty, stripped of the life it once knew. Most of the attractions have been dismantled and sold for scrap, leaving only rusting remains. Nature, uninvited, has begun to reclaim the area, creeping over decaying rides and structures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As he wanders through the silence, Fire encounters a girl. Like him, she seems drawn to the park for reasons they can barely explain. He doesn’t remember her, but she insists she remembers him. She wears a Japanese sailor school uniform, and her long braid swings behind her as she moves. Together, they spend the day exploring the desolate attractions, lost in the haze of forgotten memories.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Ant Hill</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/ant-hill/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/ant-hill/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meanwhile, in This Dimension…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After school, on her way home, Zero crouched by an ant hill, watching as the tiny workers tirelessly carried pebbles out of their tunnels, each moving with purpose. A few feet away, she noticed hundreds of ants swarming around a lollipop, likely dropped by some careless kid earlier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“They’re fascinating,” she murmured to herself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She gently reached into a nearby puddle, trying to rescue an ant struggling to stay afloat.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Hacker</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/hacker/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/hacker/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meanwhile, in Some Dimension…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fire finds himself in a featureless white room. In the center, a girl sits at a desk, working on a computer, wearing cute pastel-colored pajamas adorned with the many expressions of a recognizable cartoon character. She looks as though she’s just freshened up after a bath. Her fingers tap frenetically across the keyboard, filling the room with a rapid, satisfying rhythm in midst of the continuous humming sound of cooling fans, electrical buzzes and hard drive noises.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Day Before the Coronation</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/day-before-coronation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/day-before-coronation/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meanwhile, in That Dimension…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was the Night Day just before the Coronation Ceremony. Feeling down, Zero sat on a bench on the Hive, quietly observing the frenetic preparations for the day ahead. The Hive buzzed with life, its intricate network of corridors glowing faintly with a soft amber hue, amplifying the sense of anticipation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A strange girl sat beside her. She looked different, like an outsider. Her attire shimmered with colors that shifted with her movements, and on her head sat a peculiar “tiara” that, to Zero, seemed to whisper faint, ethereal music.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Aetherap (4Kids Opening Theme)</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/aetherap/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/aetherap/</guid><description>&lt;pre class="poem"&gt;

This story’s about Fire, fierce and untamed,
In That Dimension, where the rules are all changed.
He dreams of more, to reshape creation,
To rise as the God of Materialization!

But the world fights back, it won’t obey,
The weave unravels in disarray!
Reality snaps, the threads unwind,
A twist so wild, it fractures time!

Now the path is wrecked, no turning back,
New challengers step up—ready to attack!

Lady Zero, fearless, takes the lead,
Dives into fate with unshaken speed!

Lady Entanglement, genius, watch her break the code,
She’s building worlds while she’s in cat mode!

Lady Spiral, mysterious and deep,
She dances through chaos, secrets she keeps.

Lady Threads’s got threads for days,
She’ll knot up your mind in a million ways!

Millennium Whoop, rhythm’s off the charts,
Our beats hit hard, straight through your hearts!

Hold on tight, here it comes, let’s scream it loud!

AETHERWAY’S HERE, THE PATH’S SO CLEAR,
With this crew, you’ve got nothing to fear!

AETHERWAY! AETHERWAY! LET’S BREAK THE RULES,
We’re taking over, we’re the wildest fools!

&lt;/pre&gt;</description></item><item><title>Beach Episode</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/beach-episode/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/beach-episode/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meanwhile, in This Dimension…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Guys, guys, guys! Quick, grab your camera!” Fire shouted, his eyes sparkling with excitement. The salty breeze carried his voice through the trees, mixing with the rustling leaves and distant crash of waves. “There, there, there! What’s that? I can’t believe it—it’s a flying saucer! Heeeeeeeeeey!” he yelled from the top of a sandy hill, his shoes sinking into the soft earth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The others scrambled up, the scent of vegetation and salt filling the air. Their third-year trip—the last one before graduation—had brought them here, to this stretch of coast where the forest met the sea. Soon, life would pull them in different directions, but for now, they were just boys chasing something impossible.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Apartment Dimension 1 - Movie Night</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/apartment-dimension-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/apartment-dimension-1/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="int-cozy-living-room--night"&gt;INT. COZY LIVING ROOM – NIGHT&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A cozy but distorted ‘90s New York apartment. A CRT TV flickers between sitcoms, static, and eerie interdimensional broadcasts. A bulky beige computer hums, its screen shifting cryptic text when no one’s looking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stacks of magazines, VHS tapes, and a towering stereo. A pizza box and a cordless phone with an absurdly long antenna rest on a wobbly coffee table. Furniture floats lazily, defying gravity as if it always has.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Tonight’s Miracle</title><link>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/tonights-miracle/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://millennium-whoop.github.io/aetherway/epic/part-2/tonights-miracle/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meanwhile, in This Dimension…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;INTRO MUSIC&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ANCHOR:&lt;/strong&gt; Good evening, and welcome to &lt;em&gt;Evening Report&lt;/em&gt; . Our top story tonight—a mysterious and inexplicable encounter at a local bar that has left patrons and the owner both in shock and disbelief.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[CUT TO SCENE: Footage of the bar, with neon lights flickering and empty stools. A lower-third banner reads: “Mysterious Girl Pays It All”]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ANCHOR (V.O.):&lt;/strong&gt; It started like any other evening at this small bar. Regulars sat at their usual spots, nursing their drinks and chatting with one another. But then, something happened that no one could have predicted.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>